A Finding Aid to the Leo Castelli Gallery Records, circa 1880-2000, bulk 1957-1999, in the Archives of American Art AAA.leocast
Archives of American Art
- Exhibition Files, 1951-1999; Series 3; (Boxes 40-56, 192, 194-196, OVs 239-241, 280; 21.4 linear feet)
  - Exhibition Photographs, 1951-1998; 3.2
    - Douglas Huebler (May 15-Jun 5, 1976); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - Gianfranco Gorgoni, "Photographs" (May 22-Jun 12, 1976); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Robert Adams, "Photographs" - Castelli Graphics Exhibition (May 29-Jun 12, 1976); 4 E 77 St (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - Group Exhibition (Jun 19-Sept 10, 1976); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 16)
    - Group Drawing Exhibition (Jun 26-Sept 10, 1976); 4 E 77 St (Box 51, Folder 17)
    - Daniel Buren, "To Transgress" (Sept 15-Oct 2, 1976); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 18)
    - Robert Morris, "Black and White Felts" (Oct 9-30, 1976); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 19)
    - Kenneth Noland (Oct 23-Nov 12, 1976); 4 E 77 St (Box 51, Folder 20)
    - Claes Oldenburg (Nov 6-Dec 4, 1976); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 21)
    - Group Exhibition (Dec 11-22, 1976); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 22)
    - Poppy Johnson (Dec 11-18, 1976); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 23)
    - Andy Warhol (Jan 8-29, 1977); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 24)
    - Ellsworth Kelly (Feb 5-26, 1977); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 25)
    - Group Exhibition (Mar 5-19, 1977); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 26)
    - Louis Cane (Mar 26-Apr 16, 1977); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 27)
    - Robert Rauschenberg, "Spreads and Scales" (Apr 23-May 21, 1977); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 28)
    - "Drawings - Castelli Uptown" (May 7-28, 1977); 4 E 77 St (Box 51, Folder 29)
    - Group Exhibition (May 28-Sept 17, 1977); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 30)
    - James Rosenquist, "Recent Paintings" (Sept 24-Oct 15, 1977); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 31)
    - "Architecture I" (Oct 22-Nov 12, 1977); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 32)
    - Roy Lichtenstein, "Sculptures" (Nov 19-Dec 17, 1977); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 33)
    - William Eggleston, "Color Photographs 1966-1977" - Castelli Graphics Exhibition (Nov 25-Dec 17, 1977); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 34)
    - "Numerals 1924-1977" (Jan 7-28, 1978); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 35)
    - Billy Apple, "Extension of the Given" (Feb 4-25, 1978); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 36)
    - Bruce Nauman (Feb 4-25, 1978); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 37)
    - Donald Judd (Mar 4-25, 1978); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 38)
    - Paul Waldman (Mar 4-25, 1978); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 39)
    - Hanne Darboven, "Card-Index, Filing-Cabinet Part 1" (Apr 1-29, 1978); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 40)
    - Keith Sonnier, "Black Ground Series Drawings" (Apr 1-15, 1978); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 41)
    - Barbaralee Diamonstein, "Inside New York's Art World" (Apr 22-29, 1978); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 42)
    - Joseph Cornell, "Collages 1931-1972" (May 6-Jun 24, 1978); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 43)
    - Alan Sonfist (Jun 10-24, 1978); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 44)
    - Group Exhibition (Jul 5-Sept 23, 1978); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 45)
    - Jan Dibbets, "Structure Panoramas 1977-1978" (Sept 30-Oct 21, 1978); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 46)
    - Douglas Huebler, "Mediations" (Sept 30-Oct 21, 1978); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 47)
    - Laura Grisi (Oct 28-Nov 18, 1978); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 48)
    - Group Exhibition (Oct 28-Nov 18, 1978); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 49)
    - Frank Stella, "Indian Birds, Painted Metal Reliefs" (Jan 6-27, 1979); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 50)
    - Donald Judd, "Survey of Work" (Feb 3-24, 1979); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 51)
    - Robert Barry/Carole Gallagher, "Again and Again" (Mar 3-24, 1979); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 52)
    - Robert Morris, "6 Mirror Work" (Mar 3-24, 1979); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 53)
    - Lawrence Weiner (Mar 31-Apr 21, 1979); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 54)
    - Mia Westerlund Roosen (Mar 31-Apr 21, 1979); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 55)
    - Roy Lichtenstein, "Recent Paintings" (Apr 28-May 19, 1979); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 56)
    - Joseph Kosuth, "Text, Context, New York" (May 26-Jun 16, 1979); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 57)
    - Keith Sonnier (May 26-Jun 16, 1979); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 58)
    - Group Exhibition (Jun 23-Sept 15, 1979); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 59)
    - Richard Artschwager (Sept 22-Oct 13, 1979); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 60)
    - Dan Flavin (Oct 20-Nov 10, 1979); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 61)
    - Kenneth Noland (Nov 17-Dec 8, 1979); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 62)
    - Hanne Darboven (Jan 5-26, 1980); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 63)
    - Michele Zaza, "Neo Terrestre" (Jan 2-19, 1980); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 64)
    - Jasper Johns (Jan 19-Feb 9, 1980); 4 E 77 St (Box 51, Folder 65)
    - Barbaralee Diamonstein, "Video Interviews" (Jan 22-26, 1980); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 66)
    - Charles Gaines (Feb 2-23, 1980); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 67)
    - Salvatore Scarpitta (Feb 2-23, 1980); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 68)
    - "Leo Castelli: A New Space" (Feb 19-Mar, 1980); 142 Greene St (Box 51, Folder 69)
    - Robert Barry (Mar 1-22, 1980); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 70)
    - Nassos Daphnis, "Paintings from the 50's" (Mar 1-22, 1980); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 71)
    - Robert Rauschenberg (Mar 29-Apr 19, 1980); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 72)
    - Ellsworth Kelly (Apr 5-May 10, 1980); 142 Greene St (Box 51, Folder 73)
    - Cletus Johnson, "Theaters" (Apr 26-May 17, 1980); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 74)
    - Bruce Nauman (Apr 26-May 17, 1980); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 75)
    - James Rosenquist (May 17-Jun 21, 1980); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 76)
    - Claes Oldenburg (May 24-Jun 14, 1980); 142 Greene St (Box 51, Folder 77)
    - Claes Oldenburg (May 24-Jun 14, 1980); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 78)
    - Group Exhibition (Sept 13-Oct 18, 1980); 142 Greene St (Box 51, Folder 79)
    - Edward Ruscha, "New Paintings" (Sept 20-Oct 11, 1980); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 80)
    - Peter Young, "Homage to Agnes Martin" (Sept 20-Oct 11, 1980); 142 Greene St (Box 51, Folder 81)
    - "Architecture II: Houses for Sale" (Oct 18-Nov 22, 1980); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 82)
    - Robert Morris (Oct 25-Nov 15, 1980); 142 Greene St (Box 51, Folder 83)
    - Group Exhibition - Leo Castelli Rear Office (Nov, 1980); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 84)
    - James Turrell (Nov 22, 1980-Jan 15, 1981); 142 Greene St, 1980-1981 (Box 51, Folder 85)
    - "Drawings to Benefit the Foundation for Contemporary Performance Art Inc" (Nov 29-Dec 20, 1980); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 86)
    - Jasper Johns, "Drawings 1970-1980" (Jan 10-Feb 7, 1981); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 87)
    - Edward Ruscha, "Drawings" (Feb 14-28, 1981); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 88)
    - Lawrence Weiner (Feb 14-28, 1981); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 89)
    - Laura Grisi (Mar 7-28, 1981); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 90)
    - Paul Waldman (Mar 7-28, 1981); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 91)
    - Douglas Huebler, "Crocodile Tears" (Apr 4-May 2, 1981); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 92)
    - Julian Schnabel (Apr 4-May 2, 1981); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 93)
    - Ellsworth Kelly (Apr 11-May 9, 1981); 142 Greene St (Box 51, Folder 94)
    - "Artists' Benefit for the Trisha Brown Dance Company" (May 16-30, 1981); 142 Greene St (Box 51, Folder 95)
    - Dan Flavin, "Barred Corridors" (May 16-Sept 4, 1981); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 96)
    - Donald Judd (Sept 15-Oct 31, 1981); 142 Greene St (Box 51, Folder 97)
    - Robert Barry/Carole Gallagher, "Collaboration" (Sept 19-Oct 10, 1981); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 98)
    - Roy Lichtenstein (Oct 17-Nov 7, 1981); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 99)
    - Richard Artschwager (Nov 14-Dec 19, 1981); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 100)
    - Hanne Darboven (Nov 21-Dec 19, 1981); 142 Greene St (Box 51, Folder 101)
    - Hermine Freed, "Beads and Marbles" (Nov 21-Dec 12, 1981); 142 Greene St (Box 51, Folder 102)
    - "Eight Lithographs to Benefit the Foundation for Contemporary Performance Arts, Inc" (Nov 28-Dec 19, 1981); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 103)
    - Julian Schnabel (Nov 28-Dec 23, 1981); 142 Greene St (Box 51, Folder 104)
    - Hanne Darboven, 1982-1983, circa 1980s; (Oversized material housed in Box 196, Folder 9) (Box 51, Folder 105)
    - Hans Namuth, "Portraits" (Jan 9-Feb 13, 1982); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 106)
    - Bruce Nauman, "Violins, Violence, Silence" (Jan 9-30, 1982); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 107)
    - Andy Warhol, "Dollar Signs" (Jan 9-30, 1982); 142 Greene St (Box 51, Folder 108)
    - Andy Warhol, "Reversals" (Jan 9-30, 1982); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 109)
    - Louis Cane (Feb 6-27, 1982); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 110)
    - Claude Viallat (Feb 6-27, 1982); 142 Greene St (Box 51, Folder 111)
    - Group Exhibition (Feb 20-Mar 27, 1982); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 112)
    - Mia Westerlund Roosen (Mar 6-27, 1982); 142 Greene St (Box 51, Folder 113)
    - David Salle (Mar 6-27, 1982); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 114)
    - Sandro Chia (Mar 20-27, 1982); 142 Greene St (Box 51, Folder 115)
    - Joseph Kosuth (Apr 3-24, 1982); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 116)
    - Richard Serra (Apr 3-24, 1982); 420 W Broadway (Box 51, Folder 117)
    - Keith Sonnier (May 1-22, 1982); 420 W Broadway (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - "Castelli and His Artists, 25 Years 1982-1983" (Summer, 1982); 420 W Broadway (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Group Exhibition (Summer, 1982); 420 W Broadway (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - "25th Anniversary Exhibition of Leo Castelli" (Sept 11-Oct 9, 1982); 142 Greene St (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Barbaralee Diamonstein, "Interior Design: The New Freedom," (Oct 16-23, 1982); 142 Greene St (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Group Exhibitions (Oct 16-Nov 6, 1982); 142 Greene St (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Frank Stella (Oct 30-Nov 20, 1982); 420 W Broadway (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Salvatore Scarpitta, "American Cycle 1958-1982" (Nov 20-Dec 12, 1982); 142 Greene St (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - John Chamberlain (Nov 27-Dec 18, 1982); 420 W Broadway (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Robert Rauschenberg (Dec 31, 1982 - Jan 29, 1983); 142 Greene St, 1982-1983 (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Robert Morris, "Psychomachia" (Jan 8-29, 1983); 420 W Broadway (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Margrete Sorensen (Jan 8-29, 1983); 142 Greene St (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - Diane Blell (Feb 5-26, 1983); 142 Greene St (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - Gerard Garouste (Feb 5-26, 1983); 420 W Broadway (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - Robert Longo (Feb 5-26, 1983); 142 Greene St (Box 52, Folder 15)
    - Nassos Daphnis (Mar 5-26, 1983); 420 W Broadway (Box 52, Folder 16)
    - Douglas Huebler (Mar 5-26, 1983); 142 Greene St (Box 52, Folder 17)
    - Robert Mapplethorpe (Mar 5-23, 1983); 142 Greene St (Box 52, Folder 18)
    - Sandy Skoglund (Mar 5-26, 1983); 420 W Broadway (Box 52, Folder 19)
    - Jan Dibbets (Apr 2-23, 1983); 420 W Broadway (Box 52, Folder 20)
    - Group Exhibition (Apr 2-23, 1983); 420 W Broadway (Box 52, Folder 21)
    - Sandro Chia (Apr 30-Jun 4, 1983); 142 Greene St (Box 52, Folder 22)
    - Donald Judd (Apr 30-Jun 3, 1983); 420 W Broadway (Box 52, Folder 23)
    - Julian Schnabel (Apr 30-Jun 9, 1983); 142 Greene St (Box 52, Folder 24)
    - Michael Smith, "Mike Builds a Shelter: U.S. Government Approved Home Fallout Shelter Snack Bar" - Castelli Graphics Exhibition (May 11-Jun 30, 1983); 43 W 61 St (Box 52, Folder 25)
    - Group Exhibition (Summer, 1983); 142 Greene St (Box 52, Folder 26)
    - "Drawings/Photographs" (Jun 11-Aug, 1983); 420 W Broadway (Box 52, Folder 27)
    - Ken Price (Sept 24-Oct 15, 1983); 420 W Broadway (Box 52, Folder 28)
    - James Rosenquist (Oct 1-22, 1983); 142 Greene St (Box 52, Folder 29)
    - "Architecture III: Follies (Drawings and Models)" (Oct 22-Nov 19, 1983); 420 W Broadway (Box 52, Folder 30)
    - Roy Lichtenstein (Dec 3, 1983 - Jan 14, 1984); 142 Greene St, 1983-1984 (Box 52, Folder 31)
    - Roy Lichtenstein (Dec 3, 1983 - Jan 14, 1984); 420 W Broadway, 1983-1984 (Box 52, Folder 32)
    - Ellsworth Kelly (Jan 21-Feb 18, 1984); 420 W Broadway (Box 52, Folder 33)
    - Jasper Johns (Jan 28-Feb 25, 1984); 142 Greene St (Box 52, Folder 34)
    - Richard Serra (Feb 18-Mar 10, 1984); 420 W Broadway (Box 52, Folder 35)
    - "Artists Call Against US Intervention in Central America" (Mar 3-17, 1984); 142 Greene St (Box 52, Folder 36)
    - Edward Ruscha (Mar 3-31, 1984); 142 Greene St (Box 52, Folder 37)
    - David Salle (Mar 17-Apr 7, 1984); 420 W Broadway (Box 52, Folder 38)
    - Lucio Pozzi (Mar 31-Apr 21, 1984); 142 Greene St (Box 52, Folder 39)
    - Dan Flavin (Apr 7-May 12, 1984); 420 W Broadway (Box 52, Folder 40)
    - Paul Waldman (Apr 14-May 12, 1984); 420 W Broadway (Box 52, Folder 41)
    - Eve Sonneman (Apr 28-May 19, 1984); 142 Greene St (Box 52, Folder 42)
    - Jean-Charles Blais (May 19-Jun 9, 1984); 420 W Broadway (Box 52, Folder 43)
    - Group Exhibition (Jun 15-Jul 27, 1984); 142 Greene St (Box 52, Folder 44)
    - Group Exhibition (Jun 23-Sept 8, 1984); 420 W Broadway (Box 52, Folder 45)
    - Billy Apple, "1962-1974" (Sept 15-29, 1984); 142 Greene St (Box 52, Folder 46)
    - Hanne Darboven, "Ansichten 1982" (Sept 15-Oct 6, 1984); 420 W Broadway (Box 52, Folder 47)
    - Bruce Nauman (Oct 6-Nov 3, 1984); 142 Greene St (Box 52, Folder 48)
    - Donald Judd (Nov 17-Dec 15, 1984); 142 Greene St (Box 52, Folder 49)
    - Donald Judd (Nov 17-Dec 15, 1984); 420 W Broadway (Box 52, Folder 50)
    - Keith Sonnier (Nov 17-Dec 15, 1984); 142 Greene St (Box 52, Folder 51)
    - "Cunningham Dance Foundation Benefit Art Sale" (Nov 29-Dec 8, 1984); 420 W Broadway (Box 52, Folder 52)
    - Sandro Chia (Jan 5-26, 1985); 420 W Broadway (Box 52, Folder 53)
    - Robert Morris (Jan 12-Feb 9, 1985); 142 Greene St (Box 52, Folder 54)
    - Richard Artschwager (Feb 2-23, 1985); 420 W Broadway (Box 52, Folder 55)
    - Joseph Kosuth (Feb 3-Mar 23, 1985); 420 W Broadway (Box 52, Folder 56)
    - Nassos Daphnis (Feb 16-Mar 16, 1985); 142 Greene St (Box 52, Folder 57)
    - Ralph Gibson (Mar 2-23, 1985); 420 W Broadway (Box 52, Folder 58)
    - Francesco Clemente (Mar 30-Apr 20, 1985); 142 Greene St (Box 52, Folder 59)
    - Group Exhibition (Mar 30-Apr 13, 1985); 142 Greene St (Box 52, Folder 60)
    - Ellsworth Kelly (Mar 30-Apr 30, 1985); 420 W Broadway (Box 52, Folder 61)
    - Charles Gaines (Apr 20-May 11, 1985); 420 W Broadway (Box 52, Folder 62)
    - Gerard Garouste (Apr 20-May 11, 1985); 420 W Broadway (Box 52, Folder 63)
    - Dianne Blell (May 18-Jun 15, 1985); 420 W Broadway (Box 52, Folder 64)
    - Group Exhibition (Jun 22-Jul 27, 1985); 142 Greene St (Box 52, Folder 65)
    - Jiri Georg Dokoupil (Sept 28-Oct 19, 1985); 420 W Broadway (Box 52, Folder 66)
    - Keith Sonnier (Sept 28-Oct 19, 1985); 142 Greene St (Box 52, Folder 67)
    - Keith Haring (Oct 26-Nov 16, 1985); 142 Greene St (Box 52, Folder 68)
    - Bruce Nauman (Oct 26-Nov 16, 1985); 420 W Broadway (Box 52, Folder 69)
    - Judy Tompkins, "Silent Catalysts" (Oct 26-Nov 16, 1985); 420 W Broadway (Box 52, Folder 70)
    - Gianfranco Gorgoni (Nov 23-Dec 23, 1985); 420 W Broadway (Box 52, Folder 71)
    - Roy Lichtenstein (Nov 23-Dec 21, 1985); 420 W Broadway (Box 52, Folder 72)
    - Mario Merz (Nov 30-Dec 21, 1985); 142 Greene St (Box 52, Folder 73)
    - Hanne Darboven (Jan 11-Feb 1, 1986); 142 Greene St (Box 52, Folder 74)
    - Douglas Huebler (Jan 11-Feb 1, 1986); 420 W Broadway (Box 52, Folder 75)
    - Robert Ryman (Jan 11-Feb 1, 1986); 420 W Broadway (Box 52, Folder 76)
    - Nassos Daphnis (Feb 8-Mar 1, 1986); 420 W Broadway (Box 52, Folder 77)
    - Laura Grisi (Feb 8-Mar 1, 1986); 142 Greene St (Box 52, Folder 78)
    - Edward Ruscha (Feb 8-Mar 1, 1986); 420 W Broadway (Box 52, Folder 79)
    - Robert Combas (Mar 8-29, 1986); 420 W Broadway (Box 52, Folder 80)
    - Dan Rodan (Mar 8-29, 1986); 420 W Broadway (Box 52, Folder 81)
    - Richard Serra (Mar 8-Apr 5, 1986); 142 Greene St (Box 52, Folder 82)
    - Jean Kallina (Apr 5-May 3, 1986); 420 W Broadway (Box 52, Folder 83)
    - David Salle (Apr 5-May 3, 1986); 420 W Broadway (Box 52, Folder 84)
    - Miquel Barceló (Apr 12-May 3, 1986); 142 Greene St (Box 52, Folder 85)
    - Robert Therrien (May 10-Jun 14, 1986); 420 W Broadway (Box 52, Folder 86)
    - Joseph Kosuth (May 17-Jun 14, 1986); 142 Greene St (Box 52, Folder 87)
    - Group Exhibition (Summer, 1986); 142 Greene St (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Group Exhibition (Jun 14-Sept 13, 1986); 420 W Broadway (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Mia Westerlund Roosen (Sept 20-Oct 11, 1986); 142 Greene St (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - James Brown (Oct 4-25, 1986); 420 W Broadway (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - "Skowhegan - A Ten-Year Retrospective 1975-1985" (Oct 18-25, 1986); 142 Greene St (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Robert Rauschenberg (Oct 31-Nov 22, 1986); 420 W Broadway (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Lawrence Weiner (Nov 1-22, 1986); 142 Greene St (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Robert Therrien, "1st Installation" (Nov 5-22, 1986); 142 Greene St (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Oldenburg, van Bruggen, and Gehry, "The Course of the Knife" (Dec 13, 1986 - Jan 24, 1987); 142 Greene St), 1986-1987 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Oldenburg, van Bruggen, and Gehry, "The Course of the Knife" (Dec 13, 1986 - Jan 24, 1987); (420 W Broadway), 1986-1987 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - "XXXth Anniversary: The First Fifteen Years: Part 1" (Jan 31-Mar 7, 1987); 142 Greene St (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Jasper Johns (Jan 31-Mar 7, 1987); 420 W Broadway (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - Charles Gaines, "Numbers and Trees" (Mar 7-28, 1987); 142 Greene St (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - "XXXth Anniversary: The First Fifteen Years: Part 2" (Mar 14-Apr 4, 1987); 142 Greene St (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - Roy Lichtenstein (Mar 14-Apr 4, 1987); 420 W Broadway (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - Jean-Charles Blais (Apr 18-May 2, 1987); 142 Greene St (Box 53, Folder 16)
    - Ti Shan Hsu (Apr 18-May 9, 1987); 420 W Broadway (Box 53, Folder 17)
    - Group Exhibition, "New Work" (May 5-30, 1987); 142 Greene St (Box 53, Folder 18)
    - Robert Therrien (May 12-Jun 27, 1987); 142 Greene St (Box 53, Folder 19)
    - Group Exhibition (May 16-Jun 6, 1987); 420 W Broadway (Box 53, Folder 20)
    - "Art Against Aids" (Jun 4-13, 1987); 142 Greene St (Box 53, Folder 21)
    - Peter Schuyff (Oct 24-Nov 14, 1987); 142 Greene St (Box 53, Folder 22)
    - Meyer Vaisman (Nov 7-28, 1987); 420 W Broadway (Box 53, Folder 23)
    - Edward Ruscha (Nov 21-Dec 19, 1987); 142 Greene St (Box 53, Folder 24)
    - "Similia/Dissimilia" (Dec 5-22, 1987); 420 W Broadway (Box 53, Folder 25)
    - Chryssa, "Cityscapes, 1980-1988: Leo Castelli Gallery,", circa 1988 (Box 53, Folder 26)
    - Richard Artschwager, "Drawings" (Jan 9-30, 1988); 420 W Broadway (Box 53, Folder 27)
    - Mike Bidlo, "Picasso's Women 1907-1971" (Jan 9-30, 1988); 142 Greene St (Box 53, Folder 28)
    - Group Exhibition (Jan 9-30, 1988); 420 W Broadway (Box 53, Folder 29)
    - Robert Morris (Jan 9-30, 1988); 142 Greene St (Box 53, Folder 30)
    - Cletus Johnson (Feb 6-27, 1988); 420 W Broadway (Box 53, Folder 31)
    - Paul Waldman (Feb 6-27, 1988); 420 W Broadway (Box 53, Folder 32)
    - Nassos Daphnis (Mar 5-26, 1988); 420 W Broadway (Box 53, Folder 33)
    - "School of Visual Arts - Fine Arts Alumni 1977-1988 Selected Works" (Mar 5-12, 1988); 142 Greene St (Box 53, Folder 34)
    - Chryssa (Mar 26-Apr 16, 1988); 142 Greene St (Box 53, Folder 35)
    - Gerard Garouste (Apr 2-23, 1988); 420 W Broadway (Box 53, Folder 36)
    - James Rosenquist (Apr 23-May 14, 1988); 142 Greene St (Box 53, Folder 37)
    - Robert Therrien (Apr 30-May 21, 1988); 420 W Broadway (Box 53, Folder 38)
    - Richard Artschwager, "His Peers and Persuasions 1963-1988" (May 28-Jun 18, 1988); 142 Greene St (Box 53, Folder 39)
    - Frank O. Gehry, "Furniture" (May 28-Jul 1, 1988); 420 W Broadway (Box 53, Folder 40)
    - Edward Ruscha (May 28-Jul 31, 1988); 420 W Broadway (Box 53, Folder 41)
    - Joseph Kosuth (Sept 17-Oct 15, 1988); 578 Broadway (Box 53, Folder 42)
    - "The Last Show" (Sept 17-Oct 22, 1988); 142 Greene St (Box 53, Folder 43)
    - Mike and Doug Starn (Sept 24-Oct 15, 1988); 420 W Broadway (Box 53, Folder 44)
    - Jasper Johns, Bruce Nauman, and David Salle (Oct 5-Nov 12, 1988); 420 W Broadway (Box 53, Folder 45)
    - Bruce Nauman and Richard Serra (Oct 22-Nov 19, 1988); 578 Broadway (Box 53, Folder 46)
    - Johns Performance Foundation Benefit (Dec 8-30, 1988); 420 W Broadway (Box 53, Folder 47)
    - Robert Barry (Jan 7-28, 1989); 578 Broadway (Box 53, Folder 48)
    - Keith Sonnier (Jan 7-28, 1989); 420 W Broadway (Box 53, Folder 49)
    - Richard Artschwager (Feb 4-25, 1989); 420 W Broadway (Box 53, Folder 50)
    - David Lynch (Feb 4-25, 1989); 578 Broadway (Box 53, Folder 51)
    - Dianne Blell (Mar 4-25, 1989); 420 W Broadway (Box 53, Folder 52)
    - James Rosenquist, Joseph Kosuth, and Meyer Vaisman (Mar 4-25, 1989); 420 W Broadway (Box 53, Folder 53)
    - James Brown (Apr 1-22, 1989); 578 Broadway (Box 53, Folder 54)
    - Edward Ruscha (May 6-27, 1989); 420 W Broadway (Box 53, Folder 55)
    - Charles Simonds (May 6-27, 1989); 420 W Broadway (Box 53, Folder 56)
    - Dan Flavin (May 20-Jun 10, 1989); 578 Broadway (Box 53, Folder 57)
    - Group Exhibition (Jun 3-24, 1989); 420 W Broadway (Box 53, Folder 58)
    - Mike and Doug Starn, "Benefit to Anne Frank" (Jun 3-17, 1989); 420 W Broadway (Box 53, Folder 59)
    - Richard Serra (Sept 23-Oct 14, 1989); 420 W Broadway (Box 53, Folder 60)
    - Roy Lichtenstein, "Reflections" (Oct 2-Nov 11, 1989); 420 W Broadway (Box 53, Folder 61)
    - Roy Lichtenstein (Oct 21-Nov 11, 1989); 420 W Broadway (Box 53, Folder 62)
    - Group Drawings Exhibition (Oct 21-Nov 11, 1989); 578 Broadway (Box 53, Folder 63)
    - Miquel Barceló (Nov 18-Dec 21, 1989); 420 W Broadway (Box 53, Folder 64)
    - Miquel Barceló, "Drawings from Mali" (Nov 18-Dec 21, 1989); 578 Broadway (Box 53, Folder 65)
    - Hanne Darboven (Jan 6-27, 1990); 420 W Broadway (Box 53, Folder 66)
    - "The 60's Revisited: New Concepts/New Materials" (Jan 6-27, 1990); 578 Broadway (Box 53, Folder 67)
    - Nassos Daphnis, "Thirty Years with Leo Castelli" (Feb 3-24, 1990); 420 W Broadway (Box 53, Folder 68)
    - Douglas Huebler (Feb 3-24, 1990); 578 Broadway (Box 53, Folder 69)
    - Robert Therrien (Feb 3-24, 1990); 420 W Broadway (Box 53, Folder 70)
    - Bruce Nauman (Mar 3-24, 1990); 65 Thompson St (Box 53, Folder 71)
    - Bruce Nauman (Mar 3-31, 1990); 420 W Broadway (Box 53, Folder 72)
    - John Gutmann, "Talking Pictures: Photographs 1934-1969" (Apr 1, 1990); 578 Broadway (Box 53, Folder 73)
    - Robert Morris (Apr 3-31, 1990); 420 W Broadway (Box 53, Folder 74)
    - "Taking the Picture: Photography and Appropriation" (Apr 7-28, 1990); 578 Broadway (Box 53, Folder 75)
    - Hiroshi Teshigahara, "Echizen Ware" (Apr 7-May 12, 1990); 65 Thompson St (Box 53, Folder 76)
    - Jan Dibbets (May 5-Jun 2, 1990); 420 W Broadway (Box 53, Folder 77)
    - Group Exhibition (Jun 9-Sept 15, 1990); 420 W Broadway (Box 53, Folder 78)
    - Robert Barry (Sept 22-Oct 13, 1990); 420 W Broadway (Box 53, Folder 79)
    - James Rosenquist (Oct 20-Nov 17, 1990); 420 W Broadway (Box 53, Folder 80)
    - Claes Oldenburg/Coosje van Bruggen (Nov 27, 1990 - Jan 12, 1991); 420 W Broadway, 1990-1991 (Box 53, Folder 81)
    - Robert Watts (Nov 27, 1990 - Jan 12, 1991); 578 Broadway, 1990-1991 (Box 53, Folder 82)
    - Frank Stella, "New York" (Dec 8, 1990 - Jan 26, 1991); 65 Thompson St, 1990-1991 (Box 53, Folder 83)
    - Hanne Darboven (Jan 19-Feb 9, 1991); 578 Broadway (Box 53, Folder 84)